{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"0.19/0.007",
			"answer":"0.19/0.007",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"25.2/9",
			"answer":"25.2/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"6.3/0.003",
			"answer":"6.3/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"20.5/0.5",
			"answer":"20.5/0.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.42/0.07",
			"answer":"0.42/0.07",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.82/0.006",
			"answer":"8.82/0.006",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.632/0.4",
			"answer":"0.632/0.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"320/0.04",
			"answer":"320/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"480/0.08",
			"answer":"480/0.08",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"38.7/0.3",
			"answer":"38.7/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.1/3",
			"answer":"2.1/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9.38/7",
			"answer":"9.38/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"0.658/0.007",
			"answer":"0.658/0.007",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"12.8/0.008",
			"answer":"12.8/0.008",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.84/4",
			"answer":"1.84/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}